Johanna Baguio

Front-end Web Developer

a 29-year old Filipina finding my way to the IT industry. I was lucky enough to be given the opportunity and be a graduate of Hack Your Future Copenhagen, where I was able to maximize the resources available for me to reach my maximum potential in both back-end and front-end development. I'm a fast-learner who embraces new challenges, while striving for competence and excellence. Join me as we explore endless possibilities in this rapidly changing world of technology.



- Lauritz Hervigs vei 82, 3035 Drammen, Norway
- in linkedin.com/in/johanna-may-baguio-a8aa90174
- github.com/johbaguio

- 97337320
- johannabaguio.netlify.com
- f facebook.com/johbaguio
- instagram.com/johbaguio

EDUCATION

Bible SchoolOKS Bible school

08/2020 - 2/2020 Lillestrøm, Norway

Full Stack Web Development

Hack Your Future

08/2018 - 06/2019 Copenhagen, Denmark

Språk Kurs (A1,A2)

Folkeuniversitetet

01/2017 - 05/2017 Drammen, Norway

Bachelor of Science in Information and Communications Technology

University of San Carlos

06/2008 - 03/2013 Cebu, Philippines

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Subit

11/2019 - 2/2020 Denmark

Contact: Emil Büchler Seier - +45 26 12 36 99

Freelance Web Developer

Silent University North

10/2019 - 11/2019 Denmark silentuniversitynorth.com

Customer/Technical Service RepresentativeConvergys Philippines Incorporated

07/2013 - 01/2016

Cebu, Philippines

Achievements

- Sales Champion (May, June July, August 2015)
- Top Scorecard Achiever (January June 2015)
- Top Agent Year To Date (2015)
- Customer Service Excellence Awardee (2015)

Contact: Mr. Ronald Sara - 09157595258

SKILLS

HTML CSS Javascript Node.js React

Database Photoshop SASS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Fabric of my life (03/2019 - 06/2019)

Exess Luggage (08/2018 - 09/2018) 🗗

HYF- Quiz (12/2018 - 12/2018) 🗗

HYF-Christmas memory game (12/2018 - 01/2019) 🗹

Quote Generator (08/2019 - 08/2019) 🗹

Subit Website (11/2019 - 02/2020) 🗗

ORGANIZATIONS

Hack your Future - Copenhagen (09/2018 - 2/2020)

CERTIFICATES

Hack Your Future (09/2018 - 06/2019)

LANGUAGES

English Filipino

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

Dansk Norsk

Limited Working Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Volleyball Basketball Badminton Adventure

Travelling Music Photography